(this["webpackJsonphistory-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonphistory-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var n=r(0),o=r.n(n),c=r(3),a=r.n(c),s=r(1),i=[{question:"In which year did Great Britain recognize the independence of the United States?",answers:[{text:1776,correct:!1},{text:1783,correct:!0},{text:1781,correct:!1},{text:1778,correct:!1}]},{question:"Who was the 2nd President of the United States?",answers:[{text:"John Adams",correct:!0},{text:"Thomas Jefferson",correct:!1},{text:"Alexander Hamilton",correct:!1},{text:"James Madison",correct:!1}]},{question:"Who was the 1st Chief Justice of the U.S. Supreme Court?",answers:[{text:"John Marshall",correct:!1},{text:"Benjamin Rush",correct:!1},{text:"John Jay",correct:!0},{text:"John Adams",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which early U.S. President served in the U.S. House of Representatives after his tenure as president?",answers:[{text:"James Madison",correct:!1},{text:"John Quincy Adams",correct:!0},{text:"James Monroe",correct:!1},{text:"Alexander Hamilton",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which early U.S. Vice President killed Alexander Hamilton in a duel?",answers:[{text:"Aaron Burr",correct:!0},{text:"Thomas Jefferson",correct:!1},{text:"John Adams",correct:!1},{text:"Patrick Henry",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which cabinet position did not exist during George Washington's presidency?",answers:[{text:"Secretary of State",correct:!1},{text:"Secretary of the Treasury",correct:!1},{text:"Secretary of War",correct:!1},{text:"Secretary of Defense",correct:!0}]},{question:"In which year did the War of 1812 formally end?",answers:[{text:1812,correct:!1},{text:1815,correct:!1},{text:1814,correct:!0},{text:1813,correct:!1}]},{question:"The Louisiana Purchase occurred during which founding father's presidential administration?",answers:[{text:"John Adams",correct:!1},{text:"Thomas Jefferson",correct:!0},{text:"James Madison",correct:!1},{text:"Alexander Hamilton",correct:!1}]},{question:"Four of the first six U.S. Presidents served in which cabinet position before their presidency?",answers:[{text:"Secretary of State",correct:!0},{text:"Secretary of War",correct:!1},{text:"Secretary of the Treasury",correct:!1},{text:"Secretary of Agriculture",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which founding father served as the first U.S. Treasury Secretary?",answers:[{text:"Thomas Jefferson",correct:!1},{text:"Aaron Burr",correct:!1},{text:"Charles Pinckney",correct:!1},{text:"Alexander Hamilton",correct:!0}]}],u=o.a.createContext();function l(e){var t=Object(n.useState)(!1),r=Object(s.a)(t,2),c=r[0],a=r[1],l=Object(n.useState)(0),d=Object(s.a)(l,2),h=d[0],m=d[1],f=Object(n.useState)(i),x=Object(s.a)(f,2),b=x[0],w=x[1],y=Object(n.useState)(0),v=Object(s.a)(y,2),S=v[0],E=v[1],q=Object(n.useState)(!1),j=Object(s.a)(q,2),O=j[0],g=j[1],A=Object(n.useState)(!0),J=Object(s.a)(A,2),p=J[0],C=J[1],k=Object(n.useState)(!1),L=Object(s.a)(k,2),W=L[0],N=L[1],z=Object(n.useState)(!1),P=Object(s.a)(z,2),Q=P[0],T=P[1];return o.a.createElement(u.Provider,{value:{quizStarted:c,startQuiz:function(){a((function(e){return!e})),w((function(e){return e.sort((function(){return Math.random()-.5}))})),E(0),g(!0)},questionIndex:h,nextQuestion:function(){Array.from(document.getElementsByClassName("answer-button")).forEach((function(e){e.classList.remove("correct"),e.classList.remove("wrong")})),document.body.classList.remove("wrong"),document.body.classList.remove("correct"),N(!1),void 0===b[h+1]?(console.log("Game over"),g(!1),C(!1),T(!0)):m((function(e){return e+1}))},questions:b,score:S,incrementScore:function(){E((function(e){return e+1}))},showQA:O,showControls:p,showResult:Q,clicked:W,selectedAnswer:function(){N(!0)}}},e.children)}var d=function(){var e=Object(n.useContext)(u),t=e.questionIndex,r=e.questions;return o.a.createElement("h2",{id:"question"},r[t].question)};var h=function(){var e,t=Object(n.useContext)(u),r=t.questions,c=t.questionIndex,a=t.incrementScore,s=t.clicked,i=t.selectedAnswer,l=r[c].answers.map((function(e){return o.a.createElement("button",{key:r[c].answers.indexOf(e),className:"button answer-button",value:e.correct},e.text)}));function d(t){i(),e.forEach((function(e){e.removeEventListener("click",d)})),"true"===t.target.value?(a(),document.body.classList.add("correct"),t.target.classList.add("correct")):(document.body.classList.add("wrong"),t.target.classList.add("wrong"))}return Object(n.useEffect)((function(){e=Array.from(document.getElementsByClassName("answer-button")),!s&&e.forEach((function(e){e.addEventListener("click",d)}))}),[s]),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"button-grid"},l)};var m=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{id:"question-container"},o.a.createElement(d,null),o.a.createElement("br",null),o.a.createElement(h,null))};var f=function(){var e=Object(n.useContext)(u),t=e.quizStarted,r=e.startQuiz,c=!1===t?"control-button button":"control-button button hide";return o.a.createElement("button",{className:c,id:"start-button",onClick:function(){r()}},"Start")};var x=function(){var e=Object(n.useContext)(u),t=e.quizStarted,r=e.nextQuestion,c=!0===t?"control-button button":"control-button button hide";return o.a.createElement("button",{className:c,id:"next-button",onClick:function(){r()}},"Next")};var b=function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"controls"},o.a.createElement(f,null),o.a.createElement(x,null))};var w=function(){var e=Object(n.useContext)(u),t=e.showQA,r=e.showControls,c=e.showResult,a=e.score;return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},t&&o.a.createElement(m,null),r&&o.a.createElement(b,null),c&&o.a.createElement("h1",null,"You answered ",a," of 10 Questions Correctly!"))};r(9);a.a.render(o.a.createElement(l,null,o.a.createElement(w,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(10)},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.d2961514.chunk.js.map